#### Contact

chelsea.l.lytle@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/chelsea-I-8746709 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare

Clinical Research

# Certifications

**CNOR** 

### **Publications**

IPE Grand Rounds: A Student-led Initiative

From Interprofessional Education to Collaborative Practice: A Jefferson Alumna's Perspective

Introducing Interprofessional Education (IPE) Grand Rounds: Lessons from a New Student-led IPE Initiative

Interprofessional Education (IPE) grand rounds: Enhancing clinical relevance in medical education

A 360 Degree View of the Jefferson Health Mentors Program: Students, Administrator and Faculty Weigh in on Seven Years of Interprofessional Education

# Chelsea Lytle

Stroke Program Coordinator—MSN, RN, CNOR Houston, Texas

## Summary

Experienced Program Coordinator with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Team Building, Healthcare, Leadership, and Clinical Research. Strong community and social services professional with a Master of Science (MS) focused in Healthcare Leadership from Vanderbilt University School of Nursing.

# Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health Stroke Program Coordinator October 2018 - Present (1 year 8 months) Houston, Texas

Vanderbilt University Medical Center

3 years 4 months

Registered Nurse

July 2015 - October 2018 (3 years 4 months)

Perioperative RN Circulator and RSL on the Neurosurgery team

Nurse Intern

July 2015 - October 2015 (4 months)

I completed Vanderbilt's Perioperative nurse internship program in 2015. The program included completion of AORN's Periop101 program, lectures, and clinical training in the roles of both circulator and scrub.

Vanderbilt University
Research Assistant
January 2007 - December 2007 (1 year)

# Education

Vanderbilt University School of Nursing

Master of Science (MS), Healthcare Leadership · (2016 - 2018)

Thomas Jefferson University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing · (2013 - 2015)

Vanderbilt University
Bachelor's degree, Women and Gender Studies · (2006 - 2010)